Curriculmn Vitae Of Ms. Sakalia Julia

Personal Information:

+264 81 690 5720

kalilojulia068@gmail.com DOB: 21/08/1980

Nationality: Namibian

ID: 80082110514

PLACE OF BIRTH: Osheya, Uukolokadhi



English

Speak - 80%, Read - 80%, Write - 80%.

Oshiwam<u>bo</u>

Speak - 100%, Read - 100%, Write - 100%,

.

REFERENCES

Mr. Abisai Junias

CELL: 081 243 0486

Mr. Onesmus Kalilo

081 370 9211

Ms. Kandali Nashilongo

CELL: 081 748 0385 Windhoek

PROFILE

I am a 43-year-old female, proudly Nimbian born and raised. My passion lies in making a positive impact through my work. With a focused and determined mindset, I tackle challenges head-on and strive for excellence in all my endeavors.

★ OTHER IMPORTANT

Marital Statis: Single
Health Status: Excellent
Criminal Record: None

Strong Point: Hardwork Initiative

EDUCATION

School Attended: Okalongo Secondary School

Grade Passwd: 10 2003 Other Grade: Matriculated 2005

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Institution Attended: Flamingo Garments Pty

(Ramatex Windhoek)

Field: Machine Sewing, 2004 - 2008

Institution Attended: Mulungushi Textile and

Importers CC

Field: Machine Sewing, 2016 - 2023

Qualification: Certificate

Institution Attended: August 26

Field: Machine Sewing, 8 August 2023 - Present

Adress: Cimbebasia, Prosperita

🛊 EXTRAMURAL EXPERIENCE

Comunicational Level: Very Good

Outing: Travelling and Camping

Outdoor Activities

Socializing

Reading: Novels and Newspaper